{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "counsel",
      "answer": "勸告",
    },
    {
      "question": "crew",
      "answer": "全體人員",
    },
    {
      "question": "aviator",
      "answer": "飛行家",
    },
    {
      "question": "playwright",
      "answer": "劇作家",
    },
    {
      "question": "clergy",
      "answer": "牧師",
    },
    {
      "question": "auditor",
      "answer": "旁聽者",
    },
    {
      "question": "sculptor",
      "answer": "雕刻家",
    },
    {
      "question": "astronaut",
      "answer": "太空人",
    },
    {
      "question": "astronomer",
      "answer": "天文學家",
    },
    {
      "question": "botanist",
      "answer": "植物學家",
    },
    {
      "question": "scout",
      "answer": "偵査",
    },
    {
      "question": "caliber",
      "answer": "才能",
    },
    {
      "question": "faculty",
      "answer": "教職員",
    },
    {
      "question": "treasurer",
      "answer": "財務主管",
    },
    {
      "question": "archeologist",
      "answer": "考古學家",
    },
    {
      "question": "meteorologist",
      "answer": "氣象學者",
    },
    {
      "question": "anthropologist",
      "answer": "人類學家",
    },
    {
      "question": "imagist",
      "answer": "印象派",
    },
    {
      "question": "censor",
      "answer": "檢査員",
    },
    {
      "question": "hermit",
      "answer": "隱居者",
    },
    {
      "question": "recluse",
      "answer": "隱士",
    },
    {
      "question": "critic",
      "answer": "批評家",
    },
    {
      "question": "philanthropist",
      "answer": "慈善家",
    },
    {
      "question": "attorney",
      "answer": "辯護律師",
    }
  ]
}
